[Music]
so you just graduated all those years of
hard work have finally paid off what's
next higher studies or a rewarding
career in banking what if you can have
both in one goal ICICI Bank in
partnership with manipal global
Education Services private limited gives
you an opportunity to pursue a one-year
full-time program to become a
probationary officer at ICICI Bank and
the highlights of the course internship
and on-the-job training with stipend a
postgraduate diploma in banking
a rewarding career in sales and
relationship management
and an opportunity to serve customers
sounds like a plan
you are a graduate in any discipline and
love handling sales and customer
relationships this is your ticket to an
amazing career Journey so if you want to
be a banker and make use of a unique
opportunity to serve customers this is
the best opportunity ever apply now for
a brighter future